Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
- USW (United Steelworkers of America), Publication (Box 595, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: A USWA Action Guide: How to build an active community services program for your membership, 1975; Publication (Box 595, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Getting things done through local union committees, Publication (Box 595, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: USWA my union with pride: Building an Education Program in your local union, Publication (Box 595, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: USWA my union with pride: Problem solving for local union leadership, Publication (Box 595, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Building an eduction program in your local union, Publication (Box 595, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Building an eduction program in your local union, Publication (Box 595, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Senior Citizens against crime, 1979; Publication (Box 595, Folder 2)
    Author: USW (United Steelworkers of America). Older and Retired Workers Department
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-264
  - Item 18: USWA my union with pride: Reference Guide, Publication (Box 595, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: The steelworkers' case for wages, pension and social insurance, Publication (Box 595, Folder 2)
    Author: Philip Murray
  - Item 20: Do you have a complaint or a grievance?, Publication (Box 595, Folder 2)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-118
  - Item 21: Do you have a complaint or a grievance?, Publication (Box 595, Folder 2)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-118. Copy 2.
- USW (United Steelworkers of America), Publication (Box 595, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Agreement between W & F Mfg. Co., Inc., Buffalo, New York and United Steel Workers, Local Union No. 13711: October 31, 1978, Publication (Box 595, Folder 3)
    Author: USW (United Steelworkers of America); W and F Mfg. Co., Inc.
  - Item 2: Agreement between W & F Mfg. Co., Inc., Buffalo, New York and United Steel Workers, Local Union No. 13711: October 31, 1978, Publication (Box 595, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Wyman-Gordon Company, Inc. and United Steel Workers, AFL-CIO on behalf of Local #2285: March 30, 1980-March 27, 1983, 1980-1983 (Box 595, Folder 3)
    Author: USW (United Steelworkers of America); Wyman-Gordon Company
  - Item 4: Consolidation of Agreements as of September 1, 1977 between Wisconsin Steel Works and Progressive Steel Workers Union, Publication (Box 595, Folder 3)
    Author: Wisconsin Steel Works; Progressive Steel Workers Union
- USW (United Steelworkers of America), Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: News from the Steelworkers - Biographical sketch of Joseph Odorich, Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: News from the Steelworkers - Biographical sketch of Joseph Odorich, Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: News from the Steelworkers - Biographical sketch of Leon Lynch, Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: News from the Steelworkers - Biographical sketch of Leon Lynch, Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: News from the Steelworkers - Biographical sketch of Lloyd McBride, Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: News from the Steelworkers - Biographical sketch of Lloyd McBride, Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: News from the Steelworkers - Biographical sketch of Lynn Williams, Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: News from the Steelworkers - Biographical sketch of Lynn Williams, Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: News from the Steelworkers - Biographical sketch of Lynn Williams, Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: News from the Steelworkers - Biographical sketch of Frank McKee, Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: News from the Steelworkers - Biographical sketch of Frank McKee, Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Equality for women, Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Sexual harassment: is hazardous to you, Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: The USWA human relations procedural manual for local unions, Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
    Author: USW (United Steelworkers of America). Civil Rights Department
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-237
  - Item 15: Manual for local union civil rights committees, 1976; Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-205
  - Item 16: Manual for local union civil rights committees, 1976; Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-205. Copy 2.
  - Item 17: Report of the Committee on Future Directions of the Union: United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO-CLC: Twenty-Fourth Constitutional Convention, August 1-5, 1988, Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-280
  - Item 18: A guide to USWA Food Assistance Programs, Publication (Box 595, Folder 4)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-267-3TS
- USW (United Steelworkers of America), Publication (Box 595, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1989; Publication (Box 595, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1989; Publication (Box 595, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1990; Publication (Box 595, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Constitution, 1990; Publication (Box 595, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Constitution, 1992; Publication (Box 595, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Constitution, 1992; Publication (Box 595, Folder 5)
- USW (United Steelworkers of America), Publication (Box 595, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1986; Publication (Box 595, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Steelabour, 1979; Publication (Box 595, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.44:no.12 (1979:Oct.)
  - Item 3: The Fortieth Anniversary, '46 Strike, 1986; Publication (Box 595, Folder 6)
    Author: USW (United Steelworkers of America), Local 1005
    Notes: Special Steel Shots Supplement, July 1986.
  - Item 4: Proud heritage: a brief history of the United Steelworkers of America, 1978; Publication (Box 595, Folder 6)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-195R
  - Item 5: Proud heritage: a brief history of the United Steelworkers of America, 1978; Publication (Box 595, Folder 6)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-195R. Copy 2.
  - Item 6: Out of the crucible, Publication (Box 595, Folder 6)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR- 233
  - Item 7: Out of the crucible, Publication (Box 595, Folder 6)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-233. Copy 2.
  - Item 8: Slide Shows, Publication (Box 595, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Slide Shows, Publication (Box 595, Folder 6)
- Tampa Shipyards Inc.; Tampa Metal Trades Council, Publication (Box 596, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Tampa Shipyards Incorporated and Tampa Metal Trades Council: May 1, 1981 through April 30, 1984, 1981- 1984 (Box 596, Folder 1)
    Author: Tampa Shipyards Inc.; Tampa Metal Trades Council
- Kennecott Copper Corporation; System Federation, Publication (Box 596, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Contract - 1974, Publication (Box 596, Folder 2)
    Author: Kennecott Copper Corporation; System Federation
- USW (United Steelworkers of America), Publication (Box 596, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Summary of 1982, Basic Steel Settlement, Publication (Box 596, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Settlement agreement between the United Steelworkers of America and the Coordinating Committee Steel Companies: February 28, 1983, Publication (Box 596, Folder 3)
    Author: USW (United Steelworkers of America); Coordinating Committee Steel Companies
  - Item 3: Draft Copy - Statement of International Wage, 1983; Publication (Box 596, Folder 3)
    Author: USW (United Steelworkers of America); International Wage Policy Committee
- USW (United Steelworkers of America), Publication (Box 596, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Getting things done through local union committees, Publication (Box 596, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Union Now: Leadership in the Local Union, Publication (Box 596, Folder 4)
    Notes: Part of a conference packet.
  - Item 3: Union Now: Productive Discussion, Publication (Box 596, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Union Now: Local Union Leadership in the 80s, Publication (Box 596, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Union Now: Some Questions and Answers, Publication (Box 596, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: 50th Aniiversary Commemorative Brochure, 1986; Publication (Box 596, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Officers' Report, 1986; Publication (Box 596, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Testimony of John J. Sheehan.before the United States Senat, 1978; Publication (Box 596, Folder 4)
    Author: John J. Sheehan
  - Item 9: Union Leadership and responsibility, scholarship XIV, 1982; Publication (Box 596, Folder 4)
    Author: Alex T. Powell, Jr.
  - Item 10: Union Now: Local Union Profile, Publication (Box 596, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Problem solving for local union leadership, Publication (Box 596, Folder 4)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-235
  - Item 12: An explanation of the Employment and Income Security Program, Publication (Box 596, Folder 4)
- USW (United Steelworkers of America), Publication (Box 596, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Statement of International Wage Policy Committee, 1989; Publication (Box 596, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Lapointe Machine Tool Company and United Steelworkers of America: A Case Study, 1952; Publication (Box 596, Folder 5)
    Author: George P. Shultz; Robert P. Crisara
    Notes: Causes of Industrial Peace Under Collective Bargaining, case Study no.10
  - Item 3: The USWA human relations procedural manual for local unions, Publication (Box 596, Folder 5)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-237. Copy 2.
  - Item 4: The union is you!: the grievanceman's handbook, Publication (Box 596, Folder 5)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-116
  - Item 5: Your secret weapon: your secret ballot, Publication (Box 596, Folder 5)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-150-R
  - Item 6: Questions and Answers, Publication (Box 596, Folder 5)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR- 156
  - Item 7: We the People Say: The Right to Organize and to Have a Union is Protected by the U.S. Government, Publication (Box 596, Folder 5)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-152
  - Item 8: bumper sticker and pocket protector -- "Go Steelworkers", Publication (Box 596, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Your future is in your handsregisterland vote!, Publication (Box 596, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Ready Reference Guide for Local Union Leadership, Publication (Box 596, Folder 5)
- USW (United Steelworkers of America), Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: News from the Steelworkers - Biographical sketch of Frank McKee, Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Help Observe 50 years of Union Service 1936-1986 - a local union guide, Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Please do not buy Procter & Gamble Soap Products, Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Local union elections manual, 1975; Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: International Union Elections Manual, 1985; Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Quality of life task force economic justice report - 25th Constitutional Convention, Toronto, Canada, 1990; Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: The Free Trade Fallacy, 1983; Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
    Author: Bob Kuttner
    Notes: Pamphlet mo.PR-270. Reprinted from the New Republic, March 13, 1985
  - Item 8: Local Union action for unemployed members, Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: The union is you: the Grievance Committee handbook, Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-116. Copy 2.
  - Item 10: Steelworkers: the first fifty years - a coloring book, Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
    Author: Wendy Wudtke; Pat Finn
  - Item 11: Steelworkers: the first fifty years - a coloring book, Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: USWA Solidarity, Local 3701, Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Statement of International Wage Policy Committee, 1989; Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: 50th Anniversary Commemorative Brochure, 1986; Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Steelworkers: many faces many industries, Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-249
  - Item 16: Steelworkers: many faces many industries, Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-249. Copy 2.
  - Item 17: News from the USWA - Biographical sketch of Lloyd McBride, Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: News from the Steelworkers - Biographical sketch of Joseph Odorich, Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: News from the Steelworkers - Biographical sketch of Leon Lynch, Publication (Box 596, Folder 6)
- USW (United Steelworkers of America), Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Equality for women, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR- 238
  - Item 2: Equality for women, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR- 238. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Parliamentary Law Chart, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-106
  - Item 4: Parliamentary Law Chart, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-106. Copy 2.
  - Item 5: Parliamentary Law Chart, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-106. Copy 3.
  - Item 6: What's made by steelworkers?, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-193
  - Item 7: What's made by steelworkers?, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-193. Copy 2.
  - Item 8: We Take Pride in What We Do, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-283
  - Item 9: Please do no buy Procter & Gamble Soap Products, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: An explanation of the Employment and Income Security Program, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Civil rights guidelines, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR- 185-8TH
  - Item 12: Preserving the history of the local union, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Author: Alice M. Hoffman
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR- 212
  - Item 13: Labor's case for the ERA, 1979; Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Labor's case for the ERA, 1979; Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: The People's guide to human services, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: This is your union!, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR- 120.
  - Item 17: This is your union!, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR- 120. Copy 2.
  - Item 18: Forging a future: report of the Convention Committee on the Future Directions of the Union, 1984; Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: Healthcare for everyone, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-242
  - Item 20: United Steelworkers of America Union label program, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-263
  - Item 21: USWA Wage Department: all about us... our services..., Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-266-5TA
  - Item 22: Justice and dignity on the job: International Wage Policy Statement/1979, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
  - Item 23: An experiment in problem-solving, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-226
  - Item 24: An experiment in problem-solving, Publication (Box 596, Folder 7)
    Notes: Pamphlet no.PR-226. Copy 2.
- American Federation of Teachers, Publication (Box 597, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1992; Publication (Box 597, Folder 1)
    Author: American Federation of Teachers
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1994; Publication (Box 597, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Collective bargaining agreement between University Teachers' Union, University of Montana, and the Montana University System, July 1, 1987-June 30, 1991, 1987-1991 (Box 597, Folder 1)
    Author: University of Montana; UTU (University Teachers' Union)
  - Item 4: Agreement between the Board of Education of the School District of Philadelphia and the Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, Local 3, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO (Non- teaching assistants and house parents): September 1, 1970 to August 31, 197, 1970-1972 (Box 597, Folder 1)
    Author: Philadelphia Federation of Teachers
  - Item 5: Agreement between the Board of Education of the School District of Philadelphia and the Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, Local 3, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO (Secretaries and Other Office Employees): September 1, 1970 to August 31, 1972, 1970-1972 (Box 597, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Agreement between the Board of Education of the School District of Philadelphia and the Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, Local 3, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO (Teachers): September 1, 1970 to August 31, 1972, 1970-1972 (Box 597, Folder 1)
- American Federation of Teachers, Publication (Box 597, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Collective bargaining agreement between the Fashion Institute of Technology and United College Employees of Fashion Institute of Technology, Local 3457, American Federation of Teachers, 1990-1991 (Box 597, Folder 2)
    Author: New York (State). Office of the State Deputy Comptroller for the City of New York
  - Item 2: Agreement by and between United Cerebral Palsy Association of Western New York and United Cerebral Palsy Employees Union, NYSUT, AFT (AFL-CIO): February 21, 1977 through April 1, 1979, 1977-1979 (Box 597, Folder 2)
    Author: United Cerebral Palsy Association of Western New York; New York State United Teachers
  - Item 3: Agreement between Association for Retarded Citizens, Monmouth Unit, Inc. and Federation of N.J.A.R.C. Staff, Local 3782, New Jersey State Federation of Teachers, AFT, AFL-CIO: July 1, 1981-June 30, 1984, 1981-1984 (Box 597, Folder 2)
    Author: Association for Retarded Citizens/Monmouth Unit, Inc.; New Jersey State Federation of Teachers. Local 3782
  - Item 4: Collective bargaining agreement Association of Cincinnati Public School Office Personnel, Chapter-CFT, Local 1520, CFT, AFT, AFL-CIO, Cincinnati Board of Education: effective February 12, 1988, Publication (Box 597, Folder 2)
    Author: Association of Cincinnati Public School Office Personnel; Cincinnati (Ohio). Board of Education; Cincinnati Federation of Teachers. Local 1520
- Transportation Communications Union, Publication (Box 597, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Pan American World Airways, Inc. and Transport Workers Union of America, AFL/CIO representing Airline Mechanics and Ground Service Employees: effective July 1, 1980, Publication (Box 597, Folder 3)
    Author: Pan American World Airways, Inc.; Transport Workers Union of America
  - Item 2: Agreement between Pan American World Airways, Inc. and Transport Workers Union of America, AFL/CIO representing Airline Mechanics and Ground Service Employees: effective July 1, 1980, Publication (Box 597, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Pan American World Airways, Inc. and Transport Workers Union of America, AFL/CIO representing Commissary Employees (New York Area): effective July 1, 1980, Publication (Box 597, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Pan American World Airways, Inc. and Transport Workers Union of America, AFL/CIO representing Commissary Employees (New York Area): effective July 1, 1980, Publication (Box 597, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Pan American World Airways, Inc. and Transport Workers Union of America, AFL/CIO representing Dispatchers in the service of Pan American World Airways, Inc.: effective July 1, 1980, Publication (Box 597, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Agreement between Pan American World Airways, Inc. and Transport Workers Union of America, AFL/CIO representing Dispatchers in the service of Pan American World Airways, Inc.: effective July 1, 1980, Publication (Box 597, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Agreement between Pan American World Airways, Inc. and Transport Workers Union of America, AFL/CIO representing Commissary Employees (San Francisco, Seattle, Honolulu and Alaska): effective July 1, 1980, Publication (Box 597, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Agreement between Pan American World Airways, Inc. and Transport Workers Union of America, AFL/CIO representing Commissary Employees (San Francisco, Seattle, Honolulu and Alaska): effective July 1, 1980, Publication (Box 597, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Agreement between Pan American World Airways, Inc. and Transport Workers Union of America, AFL/CIO representing Port Stewards and Senior Port Stewards: effective July 1, 1980, Publication (Box 597, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Agreement between Pan American World Airways, Inc. and Transport Workers Union of America, AFL/CIO representing Airline Mechanics and Ground Service Employees: effective March 28, 1985, Publication (Box 597, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Constituion of the Grand Lodge Statutes for the Government of Ladges and Protective Laws, 1991; Publication (Box 597, Folder 3)
    Author: Transportation Communications Union
- Transport Workers Union of America, Publication (Box 597, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1989; Publication (Box 597, Folder 4)
    Author: Transport Workers Union of America
    Notes: UMI Print-on-Demand copy
  - Item 2: Agreement between Trans World Airlines, Inc. and the Flight Attendants in the service of Trans World Airlines, Inc. as represented by the Air Line Stewards and Stewardesses Asociation, Local 550, Transport Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, 1970; Publication (Box 597, Folder 4)
    Author: Transport Workers Union of America; Trans World Airlines; Air Line Stewards and Stewardesses Association
  - Item 3: Agreement between Trans World Airlines, Inc. and the Flight Simulator Engineers in the employ of Pan American World Airways, Inc. as represented by the Transport Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO: Effective December 24, 1980, Publication (Box 597, Folder 4)
    Author: Trans World Airlines; Pan American World Airways, Inc.; Transport Workers Union of America
  - Item 4: Agreement between Trans World Airlines, Inc. and the Flight Simulator Engineers in the employ of Pan American World Airways, Inc. as represented by the Transport Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO: Effective December 24, 1980, Publication (Box 597, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Agreement between United Airlines and Meteorologists in teh service of United Airlines as represented by Transport Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO: 1976-79, 1976-1979 (Box 597, Folder 4)
    Author: United Airlines; Transport Workers Union of America
- Transport Workers Union of America, Publication (Box 597, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1989; Publication (Box 597, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1993; Publication (Box 597, Folder 5)
- Chicagos Teachers Union, Publication (Box 598, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Delegates handbook of policies and procedures, Publication (Box 598, Folder 1)
    Author: Chicagos Teachers Union
- AFT (American Federation of Teachers), Publication (Box 598, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The college teacher and the trade union, 1936; Publication (Box 598, Folder 3)
    Author: AFT (American Federation of Teachers)
  - Item 2: Democracy in action: achievements, structure, activities, functioning [of the] N.Y. College Teachers Union, December 1937 - March 1941; a reply to the undemocratic attack on the Charter of Local 537 by the Executive Council of the American Federation of T, Publication (Box 598, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: AFT/COPE's: Clinton-Gore communications, 1992; Publication (Box 598, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: AFT/COPE's: Clinton-Gore communications, 1992; Publication (Box 598, Folder 3)
- AFT (American Federation of Teachers), Publication (Box 598, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: AFT Research Report - United Teachers of Dade ratify major contract gains, 1982; Publication (Box 598, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: AFT Research Report - Teacher supply and demand, 1981; Publication (Box 598, Folder 4)
    Notes: Report no.81.704
  - Item 3: AFT Research Report - Bureau of Labor Statistics Reports -- 1/Municipal Government Wage Surveys; 2/State and Local government Publications, 1981; Publication (Box 598, Folder 4)
    Notes: Report no.81.705
  - Item 4: AFT Research Report - Teacher supply and demand, 1981; Publication (Box 598, Folder 4)
    Notes: Report no.81.704. Copy 2.
  - Item 5: AFT Research Report - State Severance Taxes, 1981; Publication (Box 598, Folder 4)
    Notes: Report no.81.601
  - Item 6: AFT Research Report - Employment Cost Index, 1981; Publication (Box 598, Folder 4)
    Notes: Report no.81.703